
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="css/feed.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
<atom:link rel="self" href="https://www.twitter.com" />
<title>Twitter</title>
<link>https://www.twitter.com/</link>
<description>twitter_web_scrapper.py</description>
<item><title>Benedict Cumberbatch to play Pete Seeger opposite Timothée Chalamet’s Bob Dylan in ‘A COMPLETE UNKNOWN’.

Seeger was a major influence on Dylan, paving the way for his infatuation of the American folk music scene.</title><link>https://twitter.com/FilmUpdates/status/1659618884071362560</link><author>FilmUpdates</author></item>
<item><title>Benedict Cumberbatch joins the Bob Dylan biopic ‘A COMPLETE UNKNOWN’ starring Timothée Chalamet.</title><link>https://twitter.com/FilmUpdates/status/1659618657604108289</link><author>FilmUpdates</author></item>
<item><title>Auliʻi Cravalho reveals she will not reprise her role of Moana in the live action movie: “I will not be reprising the role. I believe it is absolutely vital [that] the cast accurately represents the characters and stories we want to tell.”

She will remain as executive producer.</title><link>https://twitter.com/FilmUpdates/status/1659616903755644930</link><author>FilmUpdates</author></item>
<item><title>Jacob Elordi stars in two films potentially premiering at the 2023 Venice Film Festival:

• SALTBURN (dir: Emerald Fennell) - with Barry Keoghan, Rosamund Pike, Carey Mulligan, Allison Oliver, Archie Madekwe & Ewan Mitchell

• PRISCILLA (dir: Sofia Coppola) - with Cailee Spaeny</title><link>https://twitter.com/FilmUpdates/status/1659516711433895936</link><author>FilmUpdates</author></item>
<item><title>Emerald Fennell’s SALTBURN may premiere at the Venice Film Festival.

Described as similar to ‘The Talented Mr. Ripley,’ it follows a young man (Keoghan) who develops an obsession with his classmate (Elordi).

Starring Barry Keoghan, Jacob Elordi, Rosamund Pike & Carey Mulligan.</title><link>https://twitter.com/FilmUpdates/status/1659516094460182530</link><author>FilmUpdates</author></item>
<item><title>‘INDIANA JONES AND THE DIAL OF DESTINY’ debuts with a Rotten Tomatoes score of 33% from 12 reviews so far.</title><link>https://twitter.com/FilmUpdates/status/1659510916289888258</link><author>FilmUpdates</author></item>

</channel>
</rss>
