
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="css/feed.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
<atom:link rel="self" href="https://www.twitter.com" />
<title>Twitter</title>
<link>https://www.twitter.com/</link>
<description>twitter_web_scrapper.py</description>
<item><title>The trailer for the remastered and restored edition of ‘OLDBOY’ has been released.

The film returns to theaters on August 16.</title><link>https://twitter.com/FilmUpdates/status/1656696668325134346</link><author>FilmUpdates</author></item>
<item><title>Netflix teases the sixth season of Black Mirror as “the most unpredictable, unclassifiable and unexpected [season] yet.”

Premiering this June.</title><link>https://twitter.com/FilmUpdates/status/1656696331560206336</link><author>FilmUpdates</author></item>
<item><title>Anjana Vasan, Paapa Essiedu, Katherine Rose Morley & David Shields star in BLACK MIRROR S6 episode ‘DEMON 79.’

It takes place in northern England in 1979, where a meek sales assistant is told she must commit terrible acts to prevent disaster.</title><link>https://twitter.com/FilmUpdates/status/1656695730571034624</link><author>FilmUpdates</author></item>
<item><title>Zazie Beetz, Clara Rugaard & Danny Ramirez star in BLACK MIRROR S6 episode ‘MAZEY DAY.’

It follows a troubled starlet who is dogged by invasive paparazzi while dealing with the consequences of a hit-and-run incident.</title><link>https://twitter.com/FilmUpdates/status/1656695356002824193</link><author>FilmUpdates</author></item>
<item><title>Aaron Paul, Josh Hartnett, Kate Mara, Auden Thornton & Rory Culkin star in BLACK MIRROR S6 episode ‘BEYOND THE SEA.’

It takes place in an alternate 1969, where two men on a perilous high-tech mission wrestle with the consequences of an unimaginable tragedy.</title><link>https://twitter.com/FilmUpdates/status/1656695069745856516</link><author>FilmUpdates</author></item>
<item><title>Samuel Blenkin, Myha'la Herrold, Daniel Portman, John Hannah & Monica Dolan star in BLACK MIRROR S6 episode ‘LOCH HENRY.’

It follows a couple who travel to a Scottish town to work on a nature documentary but find themselves drawn to a juicy local story involving shocking events.</title><link>https://twitter.com/FilmUpdates/status/1656694727759020032</link><author>FilmUpdates</author></item>
<item><title>Annie Murphy, Salma Hayek, Michael Cera, Rob Delaney, Ben Barnes & Himesh Patel star in BLACK MIRROR S6 episode ‘JOAN IS AWFUL.’

The story of an average woman who discovers a streaming platform launched a prestige TV adaptation of her life, where she is portrayed by Salma Hayek.</title><link>https://twitter.com/FilmUpdates/status/1656694201428344833</link><author>FilmUpdates</author></item>

</channel>
</rss>
