
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="css/feed.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
<atom:link rel="self" href="https://www.twitter.com" />
<title>Twitter</title>
<link>https://www.twitter.com/</link>
<description>twitter_web_scrapper.py</description>
<item><title>Isabelle Huppert and Finn Wittrock to star in home invasion thriller ‘Free Radicals.’

It revolves around the harrowing encounter between an ailing woman (Huppert) and a killer on the run (Wittrock).

(https://deadline.com/2023/05/isabelle-huppert-finn-wittrock-join-free-radicals-thriller-cannes-1235363841/…)</title><link>https://twitter.com/FilmUpdates/status/1657055009287155712</link><author>FilmUpdates</author></item>
<item><title>Emma Seligman’s ‘BOTTOMS’ starring Rachel Sennott, Ayo Edebiri, Zamani Wilder, Summer Campbell, Havana Rose Liu, Nicholas Galitzine, Virginia Tucker, Kaia Gerber and Marshawn Lynch will be released in theaters on August 25.</title><link>https://twitter.com/FilmUpdates/status/1657052726335881217</link><author>FilmUpdates</author></item>
<item><title>“… and then started to look into who you were and what you'd done, and got very excited about the idea of meeting you, and having you screen test for Batman [Begins].”</title><link>https://twitter.com/FilmUpdates/status/1657051159461240832</link><author>FilmUpdates</author></item>
<item><title>Christopher Nolan on seeing Cillian Murphy for the first time:

“I saw a picture of you with your shaved head and your crazy eyes — no offense. I remember being struck by your presence, from that one photograph…”</title><link>https://twitter.com/FilmUpdates/status/1657051153203359749</link><author>FilmUpdates</author></item>
<item><title>Source:</title><link>https://twitter.com/FilmUpdates/status/1657048406634766336</link><author>FilmUpdates</author></item>
<item><title>Halle Bailey says Jodi Benson, who voiced Ariel in the animated THE LITTLE MERMAID, told her “how proud she was of me and how I’m handling everything.”

“I appreciate her for being so warm and welcoming because she’s the GOAT, it was important to me to get her stamp of approval.”</title><link>https://twitter.com/FilmUpdates/status/1657048357041238025</link><author>FilmUpdates</author></item>

</channel>
</rss>
