
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="css/feed.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
<atom:link rel="self" href="https://www.twitter.com" />
<title>Twitter</title>
<link>https://www.twitter.com/</link>
<description>twitter_web_scrapper.py</description>
<item><title>Shangela denies rape allegations, calling them “entirely meritless” following a civil lawsuit filed on Wednesday.

Former ‘We’re Here’ production assistant Daniel McGarrigle claims Shangela raped him while filming the HBO series’ first season in 2020.

: https://today.com/popculture/tv/drag-race-star-shangela-accused-rape-new-lawsuit-rcna82904?cid=sm_npd_td_fb_ma…</title><link>https://twitter.com/PopCrave/status/1654287173838073856</link><author>popcrave</author></item>
<item><title>Kali Uchis has teamed up with Fortnite for her own “I Wish You Roses” map.</title><link>https://twitter.com/PopCrave/status/1654276190872510465</link><author>popcrave</author></item>
<item><title>Billboard announces new “fan packs” rule for bundles that limits artists to two options per album release.

Items must be available separately, offerings must be approved in advance, and digital download bundles will not count.

: https://billboard.com/pro/billboard-fan-packs-album-charts/…</title><link>https://twitter.com/PopCrave/status/1654244874009591808</link><author>popcrave</author></item>
<item><title>New look at Pedro Pascal and Ethan Hawke in Pedro Almodóvar’s queer western, ‘Strange Way of Life.’</title><link>https://twitter.com/PopCrave/status/1654229266962452480</link><author>popcrave</author></item>
<item><title>#GotGVol3 utilizes music in such a powerful way, specifically with a Florence + The Machine track that will leave audiences in tears.</title><link>https://twitter.com/PopCrave/status/1654224313275518976</link><author>popcrave</author></item>
<item><title>#GotGVol3 is the MCU’s most disturbing and emotionally intense film yet, but James Gunn manages to balance this out with his beloved style of comedy.

The movie feels like an epic grand finale for our favorite space heroes, with each member getting the chance to shine and fully… Show more</title><link>https://twitter.com/PopCrave/status/1654220647734837249</link><author>popcrave</author></item>

</channel>
</rss>
