
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="css/feed.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
<atom:link rel="self" href="https://www.twitter.com" />
<title>Twitter</title>
<link>https://www.twitter.com/</link>
<description>twitter_web_scrapper.py</description>
<item><title>The Weeknd to 
@WMag
 on his past hair and people’s comments on it:

“The hair became an obstacle for me! I went from ‘No one knows who I am’ to ‘Nobody has that hair except The Weeknd.’ I was always trying to hide it. When I finally decided to cut it, everybody said, ‘Don’t do… Show more</title><link>https://twitter.com/PopCrave/status/1655610112097103873</link><author>popcrave</author></item>
<item><title>The Weeknd tells 
@WMag
 that his next album will likely be his last as The Weeknd:

“I’m getting ready to close the Weeknd chapter. I’ll still make music, maybe as Abel, maybe as The Weeknd. But I still want to kill The Weeknd… This is something that I have to do. As The Weeknd,… Show more</title><link>https://twitter.com/PopCrave/status/1655608514578984975</link><author>popcrave</author></item>
<item><title>Taylor Swift refused to cancel her final Nashville show and performed in the pouring rain after a four-hour lightning delay.</title><link>https://twitter.com/PopCrave/status/1655605325670612996</link><author>popcrave</author></item>
<item><title>Taylor Swift and Matty Healy have been seeing each other after Jack Antonoff reconnected them, 
@ETnow
 reports:

“[They] like each other. Taylor has a crush on Matty and they are having a good time hanging out. Matty also thinks Taylor is awesome and incredibly talented, too.”… Show more</title><link>https://twitter.com/PopCrave/status/1655587238808281088</link><author>popcrave</author></item>
<item><title>“Moonlight” by 
@KaliUchis
 has reached 100 MILLION streams on Spotify.

It’s her 13th song to achieve this.</title><link>https://twitter.com/PopCrave/status/1655581261543403521</link><author>popcrave</author></item>
<item><title>Lily-Rose Depp tells 
@WMag
 she was thinking about Britney Spears, Beyoncé, Mariah Carey and “every huge pop star of our time” for her role as Jocelyn in ‘THE IDOL’:

“I wanted Jocelyn to be the kind of woman who can dominate a room, someone who doesn’t ever shy away from their… Show more</title><link>https://twitter.com/PopCrave/status/1655565993781911555</link><author>popcrave</author></item>

</channel>
</rss>
